Hey Hello Namaskar Welcome back to my YouTube
channel HD Solutions So today I am going to tell you guys about
this 16 Company
General Insurance, this is its dashboard. Okay,
after making a policy, whether it is your two
wheeler or commercial vehicle or
private car, whatever the insurance is, it is
mandatory to do KYC for it. If
your KYC is done in the portal itself, then it is a good
thing. If sometimes in the RC there is MD
or Mr or Free
or MRS, then the name which is in the RC is
not the same as in the PAN card or Aadhar card of the customer, then
what happens sometimes due to it not being exact,
KYC fails, meaning it appears that do more
KYC verification,
follow the instructions and finish the verification, then
avoid policy cancellation, you
can proceed with the policy process. Now
such a message comes in 16 MS Company,
meaning KYC verification fails
and it is written in it that
a link will be sent to the customer care mobile through SMS.
Through that link, you people will be able to cancel the policy.
KYC will have to be done, if you guys do
n't do it within 10 days then your policy can also be cancelled,
okay your policy can also be cancelled,
if it doesn't happen then you don't do KYC, so
[Music]
after that see, when your policy is made
without KYC then it is written like this that
policy generated rasgulla, your policy has been
generated successfully,
but see in this KYC
verification pending, it goes into pending,
if your KYC verification is not done due to PAN card and name in RC or
some other reason, it
remains pending,
so what happens is an SMS goes to the customer's
mobile, he gets
a link in the SMS, through that link
how will you guys do KYC, I mean
today I am going to share the same video with you guys,
if you are visiting my channel for the first time then don't
forget to subscribe to the channel and also press the bell icon
of Dhaba and on the notification
so that the next time I upload a video, you can get the
notification first, so let's move
towards the mobile screen  Let's see
how the message went to the customer's mobile
and how the link is made through it and this
video is this, I had made a 16 ms video, I will
also put this 16 ms video
in the description box for you guys,
go and watch this video first, there is such a
policy, what happens after the policy is made, this is what happens,
KYC remains pending,
see it remains in the pending,
after that the link is sent to the customer's mobile,
if you face such a problem that KYC is
not done, KYC goes into pending, instantly a
message will be sent to the mobile number which you had given in the policy on the customer's mobile, by doing this
a message will come on the mobile that dear customer
record should be
with you and
after clicking on register in Aadhaar of the customer, this 16 ms has come to people,
KYC is visible in it,
you will now have its KYC,
so stay tuned to the video, it is
loading, see in it let's
fair file and identity first and easy
security and privacy, after that
see the blue colored gate below  It is started,
you have to click on it,
after clicking, see this and Aadhar link with
your phone number, yes my phone number
is linked in Aadhar, so the mobile number of the customer in the Aadhar card
should be in your hand, after that see, we will do it through this
technique, then
you people will have to click on the blue color in it,
after clicking, see such an
interface will open,
in this you people have to enter the Aadhar number of the customer,
after that you have to carefully fill in the apps of the code which is below,
but after clicking on next, the
registered OTP of the customer will be sent
on the customer's mobile, so
after entering the OTP, you people have to click on continue,
after clicking on continue, you have to
keep any one pin in it, Sethi and Diesel Locker
security pin, if you will also feel it,
you people can open it through the screen,
I put any 6 digital pin,
after that click on continue,
after this click, it is loading,
see this is the KYC of 16  This is done through diesel loan. The
link that comes on the customer's mobile is
instantly transferred through the link. If your
KYC is not complete, then you
can do it through Aadhar card, through mobile notification.
How did you like my video? If you liked the video, then
share it with other people
and if you have come to my channel for the first time, then do
not forget to subscribe to the channel and
also press the bell icon on all the notifications of Dhaba.